Hearst.com Privacy Notice
=========================

Last Updated: March 13, 2026

This Privacy Notice (the “Privacy Notice”) describes how Hearst Communications, Inc. and its affiliates and subsidiaries (“we”, “us”, “our” or “Hearst”) handle personal information in connection with the operation of the Hearst corporate website available at [www.hearst.com](http://hearst.com/) and linking to this Privacy Notice (the “Site”).

**Hearst is one of the nation’s largest global diversified information, services, and media companies. You can learn more about the media, transportation, health, entertainment and other brands and businesses (“Hearst Businesses”) within our portfolio by navigating to the “Businesses” tab at the top of this page. Please note that this Privacy Notice applies only to information that Hearst obtains in connection with the operation of this Site and describes how we collect and process the personal information we obtain from the Site and with whom we may share it; it does not apply to the sites and services of the Hearst Businesses. The Site is made available for informational and research purposes. For more information about how the Hearst Businesses use personal information they obtain in connection with their sites and services, please review the privacy notice for each Hearst Business you have interacted with. The privacy notice for a Hearst Business you have interacted with is generally accessible by navigating to the footer of the applicable site and clicking on the “Privacy Notice” link.**

Hearst’s privacy practices may vary among the countries in which we operate to reflect local practices and legal requirements, and specific privacy notices apply in certain countries or regions. Please visit the corporate site of the specific country or region to learn more about our privacy practices in relation to that country or region.

**WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION WE OBTAIN**

Hearst obtains different types of information, including personal information, when you use the Site. This may include information that directly identifies you, such as your name and contact information (this type of information may be called “personal information,” “personal data,” or “personally identifiable information). We and our service providers may aggregate or anonymize information that we collect in connection with your use of this Site; this information is not “personal information,” “personal data,” or “personally identifiable information.”

The information we obtain generally consists of information (1) you give us about yourself, such as when you complete a form on the Site, (2) we obtain from other sources or (3) automatically collected about your interactions with the Site from your browser or mobile device using technologies such as cookies.

**Information you give us or we obtain from other sources:**

We may ask you to provide your personal information when you use the Site, such as when you sign up to our Hearstlink Newsletter, or complete a form on the Site. You may not be able to use certain features if you choose not to submit the requested information.

The personal information you give us may include details such as:

*   Contact information (e.g., name, email address, company name and address).
*   Demographic and interests information (e.g., region, interests and preferences).
*   Other information you choose to share with us (e.g., when you submit a form).
*   Transactional and activity information (e.g., requests and searches).

**Information automatically collected:**

We and our service providers (partners) may automatically obtain certain information when you access the Site from your web browser or mobile device, such as information about the number and frequency of visitors, technical information about browsers and devices used to access the Site, and information about crashes or other technical issues. In addition, we and our service providers (partners) may automatically collect certain information through automated means about your activities over time across the browsers and devices you use to access the Site as well as across third-party sites, apps or other media. These technologies may assign or collect a unique identifier on your browser or device, and may reside, among other places, on your computer or device, within webpages or mobile apps. We may use these technologies to administer the Site, understand usage of the Site and improve the content and offerings of the Site.

The information automatically collected may include: 

*   Information about your computer, device, browser and operating system (e.g., type, model, or version).
*   Internet protocol (IP) address, which may be used to derive your general geographic area (e.g., city and country).
*   Information about your interactions with the Site, including browsing and search activities and clickstream data that reflect the content and website features you have accessed, clicked on, viewed, watched, or otherwise interacted with.
*   Information about how you accessed the Site, including details about websites or apps visited immediately before or after accessing the Site.

**HOW WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION WE OBTAIN**

Hearst may use the personal information we obtain in connection with the operation of the Site for a number of purposes, including, but not limited to:

*   Providing you with the Site, as well as information you may request.Communicating with you, including by sending you marketing and advertising communications.
*   Developing and improving the Site and the services we provide and customizing the user experience.
*   Generating and analyzing statistics about your use of the Site and our offerings.
*   Performing audits, assessments, and testing or troubleshooting activities. 
*   Backing up our systems (including for disaster recovery purposes) and enhancing the security of the Site .
*   Detecting, preventing, and responding to fraud or potentially illegal activities, violations of this Privacy Notice or the Terms of Use, violations of law, intellectual property infringement, or other misuse of the Site. 
*   Complying with and enforcing applicable industry and legal requirements (including legal process such as court orders, warrants or subpoenas).

**HOW WE PROVIDE PERSONAL INFORMATION TO OTHERS**

Hearst may provide the information we obtain from you through the Site to:

*   Our affiliates and subsidiaries as necessary or appropriate. 
*   With your consent or otherwise at your direction. 
*   With service providers (partners) that provide services or handle transactions on our behalf. These services include cloud computing, monitoring and maintaining information security, email distribution, and analytics. 
*   As we believe is necessary or appropriate to protect, enforce, or defend our legal rights, the privacy or safety of our employees, users of the Site or other individuals and entities, or to comply with or enforce applicable law or legal process, including responding to court orders, warrants, subpoenas and other requests from public and government authorities.

We also reserve the right to transfer any of the information we have about you to proceed with the consideration, negotiation, or completion of a sale or transfer of all or a portion of our business or assets to a third party, such as in the event of a merger, acquisition or other disposition, or in connection with a bankruptcy reorganization, dissolution, or liquidation. We may share your information with third parties when you consent to or request such sharing.

**YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS, INCLUDING MARKETING OPT-OUTS**

This section provides the privacy rights you may have in connection with your use of the Site. If you have interacted with a Hearst Business, you can learn more about the privacy rights you may have with respect to that Hearst Business by reviewing their privacy notice. The privacy notice for a Hearst Business you have interacted with is generally accessible by navigating to the footer of the applicable site and clicking on the “Privacy Notice” link. 

Below you will find information on how to submit privacy rights requests to the consumer media brands and businesses that you may have interacted with, which make up the Hearst affiliated network of media companies: 

*   To submit your request for **Hearst Magazines**, please complete the form available at accessprivacy@hearst.com; to request to opt out of “sale” or “targeted advertising” practices based on cookies and similar technologies, click on the link labeled “Your Privacy Choices (Opt Out of Sale/Targeted Ads)” available in footer of the applicable Hearst Magazines site you have interacted with.  
*   To submit your request for **Hearst Newspapers**, please visit the site of the applicable Hearst Newspaper(s) you have interacted with and complete the form available by selecting the footer link labeled “Your Privacy Choices (Opt Out of Sale/Targeted Ads).” 
*   To submit your request for **Hearst Television**, please visit the site of the applicable Hearst Television properties you have interacted with and complete the form available by selecting the footer link labeled “Your Privacy Choices (Opt Out of Sale/Targeted Ads).”   

**Your U.S. State Privacy Rights**

Residents of states with applicable privacy laws are afforded certain rights with respect to their personal information. Depending on where you live, and subject to certain exceptions, you may be entitled to the rights described below with respect to the data we collect through the Site. Please note that if you submit a request to exercise any of the below rights (a “Privacy Rights Request”), we may request additional information to enable us to process your request. We will use the information you provide to make Privacy Rights Requests to verify your identity, locate your personal information that we may hold about you, and to fulfill your request. Except as otherwise directed below, please contact us at [hearstsiterequests@hearst.com](mailto:hearstsiterequests@hearst.com) to exercise your privacy rights.

1.  **Right to access your personal information**. Under applicable privacy laws, you have the right to know the types and the specific pieces of the personal information we have collected from you through the Site.
2.  **Right to delete your personal information**. In some circumstances, you may ask us to delete personal information we collected from you through the Site. Please note that this is not an absolute right under applicable privacy laws, and we may not be able to delete all or some of your personal information.
3.  **Right to correct your personal information.** You may request that we modify or update your personal information that we have collected from you through the Site if it is inaccurate. Please be aware that not all personal information is able to be corrected, and we reserve the right to deny a request to correct your information where exceptions apply. Please note that if you would like to correct the email you use to receive newsletters from us, you must unsubscribe from the newsletters and re-subscribe using your preferred email address.
4.  **Right to opt out**. Applicable privacy laws may provide you with the right to limit or opt out of the use of your personal information for certain purposes.

_Right to Opt Out of Sale/Targeted Advertising_: Certain state privacy laws provide eligible residents with the right to opt out of the “sale” or “sharing” of your personal information for “targeted advertising” purposes, as such terms are defined under applicable privacy laws. At this time we do not engage in activities considered the “sale” or “sharing” of personal information as defined by applicable law in connection with the personal information we have collected about you through this Site. 

_Rights Regarding Sensitive Personal Information_: Certain pieces of personal information that we have about you may be considered “sensitive” under applicable laws. Depending on where you live, and subject to exceptions, you may have certain rights to opt in or opt out/limit the processing of personal information that may be considered sensitive under applicable privacy laws. Please note that we do not collect, use, or disclose “sensitive” personal information through the Site.

5.  **Right to be free from discrimination**. You may exercise any of the above rights without fear of being discriminated against.

For additional information regarding our California-specific data practices, please see the section below titled [Notice at Collection/ Additional Information for California Residents](#_ADDITIONAL_INFO).  

**Authorized Agents**

You may designate an authorized agent to make a request in relation to the privacy rights listed above. In the request, you or your authorized agent must provide us with sufficient information for us to verify both the identity of your agent and that your agent has been authorized to act on your behalf. This may result in your Privacy Rights Request taking additional time to process. If you are an authorized agent working on behalf of a consumer, you will need to follow the above processes and email [hearstsiterequests@hearst.com](mailto:hearstsiterequests@hearst.com).

**Privacy Rights Appeal Process**

Certain US state privacy laws afford eligible residents the right to appeal a denial of a Privacy Rights Request in whole or in part.  For additional information regarding how to submit a Privacy Rights Request appeal, please email [hearstsiterequests@hearst.com](mailto:hearstsiterequests@hearst.com).

**MARKETING AND ADDITIONAL OPT OUT METHODS**

**Email Marketing**

You may unsubscribe from our marketing communications and newsletters by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link in each email.

**Google Analytics**

To opt out of Google Analytics on your browser or device, please visit [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) and follow the instructions.

**DO NOT TRACK/GLOBAL PRIVACY CONTROL**

Hearst does not currently take steps to respond to browsers’ “Do Not Track” signals as no uniform standard to respond to such signals has been developed at this time. As noted above, we do not currently “sell” or “share” personal information in connection with the Site, and therefore this Site does not detect opt out preferences like the  Global Privacy Control (“GPC”).

**HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION**

We maintain reasonable administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect the personal information we obtain through the Site. However, no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we make reasonable efforts to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**NON-U.S. VISITORS**

We operate the Site from the United States. Any information we obtain about you in connection with your use of the Site may be processed and stored in the United States or other countries.

**LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES, MOBILE APPS OR OTHER SERVICES**

The Site may contain links to third-party websites, mobile apps or features, including through social media features and widgets on our Site. Hearst is not responsible for the collection or use of your information by such third parties. We encourage you to review the privacy policies or other similar statements applicable to third-party websites, mobile apps or features.

**NOTICE AT COLLECTION/ADDITIONAL INFORMATION FOR CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS**

**Your California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”) Rights**

The California Consumer Privacy Act, as amended by the California Privacy Rights Act of 2020 (“CCPA”) requires specific disclosures for each category of personal information that we collect and may provide to others. The table below summarizes our general data handling practices, which are more fully described in this Privacy Notice above.

Notes about the information in the table below: 

*   Not all the listed categories of information below will necessarily be collected or received about every individual.
*   Not all examples of a particular “category of personal information” will necessarily be collected or received about every individual. 
*   Personal Information handling practices may differ depending on how you interact with the Site. 

|     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| **Category of Personal Information** | **Categories of Sources** | **Business or Commercial Purpose for Collecting and Providing the Category of Personal Information** | **Categories of Third Parties and Other Entities to Which We Provide Personal Information** |
| Identifiers ((§1798.140 (v)(1)(A) and (B)), which include: (i) your contact information and other identifiers (e.g., name, phone number,); and (ii) online identifiers<br><br>(e.g., Internet Protocol (IP) address, device identifiers); | ·         Directly from you<br><br>·         Collected or observed through Automated Means | Please refer to the purposes described in the “How We Use Personal Information We Obtain” section above | ·         With affiliates and subsidiaries<br><br>·         With service providers<br><br>·         With government authorities as required by law or as necessary to protect our rights |
| Internet or other electronic network activity information (§1798.140 (v)(1)(F)), which include browsing history, search history, and how you use, access, or interact with the Site. | ·         Directly from you<br><br>·         Collected or observed through Automated Means | Please refer to the purposes described in the “How We Use Personal Information We Obtain” section above | ·          With affiliates and subsidiaries<br><br>·         With service providers<br><br>·         With government authorities as required by law or as necessary to protect our rights |
| Professional or Employment-Related Information (§1798.140 (v)(1)(I)) which includes information your employment-related contact information (e.g.  your professional email and phone number and office address). | ·         Directly from you | Please refer to the purposes described in the “How We Use Personal Information We Obtain” section above | ·         With affiliates and subsidiaries<br><br>·         With service providers<br><br>·         With government authorities as required by law or as necessary to protect our rights |

For each of the categories listed above, we will retain your personal information for as long as needed or permitted, depending on the purpose for obtaining that data and consistent with applicable laws. We will keep your personal information for as long as we have a relationship with you (e.g. to provide you with the newsletters you subscribe to). Once our relationship with you has come to an end, we will retain your personal information for a period of time that enables us to:

*   Maintain business records for analysis, understanding market trends, and/or audit purposes.
*   Comply with record retention requirements under applicable laws or other relevant legal or regulatory requirements.
*   Defend, establish, exercise, or bring any existing or potential legal claims.
*   Carry out fraud detection and prevention.
*   Address any complaints.

Residents of California may have the following rights:

1\. Right to access your personal information.  Under the CCPA, you have the right to:

*   Know the categories of personal information, which we collect from you through the Site and the categories of sources from which we got the information
*   Know the business or commercial purposes for which we collect and provide personal information to others
*   Know the categories of third parties and other entities to whom we provide personal information; and
*   You may request to access the specific pieces of personal information that we collected about you through this Site.  

2\. Right to deletion.  Subject to certain exceptions, you may ask us to delete the personal information we collected about you through this Site. Please note that this is not an absolute right under applicable privacy laws, and we may not be able to delete all or some of your personal information. 

3\. Right to **correct your personal information**.  You may request that we modify or update your personal information that we have collected from you through the Site if it is inaccurate. Please be aware that not all personal information is able to be corrected, and we reserve the right to deny a request to correct your information where exceptions apply. Please note that if you would like to correct the email you use to receive newsletters from us, you must unsubscribe from the newsletters and re-subscribe using your preferred email address. 

4\. Right to opt out. Applicable privacy laws may provide you with the right to limit or opt out of the use of your personal information for certain purposes.

*   _Right to Opt Out of Sale/Targeted Advertising_: Certain state privacy laws provide eligible residents with the right to opt out of the “sale” or “sharing” of your personal information for “targeted advertising” purposes, as such terms are defined under applicable privacy laws. At this time we do not engage in activities considered the “sale” or “sharing” of personal information as defined by applicable law in connection with the personal information we have collected about you through this Site. 
*   _Right to Limit Processing of Sensitive Personal Information_: Certain pieces of personal information are defined as “sensitive” under applicable privacy laws, and privacy laws afford eligible residents with the right to limit the use of such sensitive personal information only for certain purposes. Please note that we do not collect, use, or disclose “sensitive” personal information through the Site.

5\. Right to be free from discrimination.  You may exercise any of the above rights without fear of being denied goods or services.  

If you would like to exercise your CCPA rights with respect to the personal information we collected about you through this Site, please contact us by email at [hearstsiterequests@hearst.com](mailto:hearstsiterequests@hearst.com).

This section provides the privacy rights you may have in connection with your use of the Site. If you have interacted with the Hearst Businesses, please review their respective privacy notices to learn more about privacy rights you may have in connection with those brands and businesses. The privacy notice for a Hearst Business you have interacted with is generally accessible by navigating to the footer of the applicable site and clicking on the “Privacy Notice” link.   
Below you will find information on how to submit privacy rights requests to the consumer media brands and businesses that you may have interacted with, which make up the Hearst affiliated network of media companies: 

*   To submit your request for **Hearst Magazines**, please complete the form available at accessprivacy@hearst.com; to request to opt out of “sale” or “targeted advertising” practices based on cookies and similar technologies, click on the link labeled “Your Privacy Choices (Opt Out of Sale/Targeted Ads)” available in footer of the applicable Hearst Magazines site you have interacted with.  
*   To submit your request for **Hearst Newspapers**, please visit the site of the applicable Hearst Newspaper(s) you have interacted with and complete the form available by selecting the footer link labeled “Your Privacy Choices (Opt Out of Sale/Targeted Ads).” 
*   To submit your request for **Hearst Television**, please visit the site of the applicable Hearst Television properties you have interacted with and complete the form available by selecting the footer link labeled “Your Privacy Choices (Opt Out of Sale/Targeted Ads).” 

**Minors**

The Site is not intended for use by those under 18 and we do not knowingly collect or disclose personal information of minors under the age of 18.

**Your Shine the Light California Rights (CA Civil Code § 1798.83)**

The California “Shine the Light” law allows California residents the right to request a list of third parties to which certain personal information (as defined by California Civil Code § 1798.83) obtained through the Site was disclosed to others by Hearst during the preceding year for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes. We do not disclose such personal information to third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. 

**INTERNATIONAL DATA TRANSFERS**

Information collected through this Site will be processed in and subject to the laws of the United States, which may not provide the same level of protection for your personal information as your home country.

**CAREERS/JOB OPPORTUNITIES**

This Privacy Notice does not apply to web pages hosting our careers or job opportunities. Any information obtained through such pages is governed by the privacy notice published thereon.

**DISPUTE RESOLUTION/TERMS OF USE**

Any dispute concerning the Site (including our use of your personal information) will be resolved per the dispute resolution provision in the [Terms of Use](https://www.hearst.com/-/hearst-com-terms-of-use), which govern your use of the Site. Please take a few minutes to read the Terms of Use before using the Site.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY NOTICE**

We may update this Privacy Notice from time to time to reflect changes in our privacy practices or applicable laws. We may, as permitted by law, make such changes without prior notice. We will publish the updated version on the Site and indicate at the top of the Privacy Notice when it was most recently updated. Your use of the Site will be governed by the current version of this Privacy Notice.

**CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice or, in accordance with applicable laws, you would like to review or request changes to personal information collected in connection with your use of the Site, please contact us at [hearstsiterequests@hearst.com](http://hearstsiterequests@hearst.com/).
